<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>BigLedger - Complete Business Management Platform – Industry Solutions</title><link>https://www.bigledger.com/user-guide/industry-solutions/</link><description>Recent content in Industry Solutions on BigLedger - Complete Business Management Platform</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="https://www.bigledger.com/user-guide/industry-solutions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Automotive and Workshop Industry</title><link>https://www.bigledger.com/user-guide/industry-solutions/automotive-and-workshop-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.bigledger.com/user-guide/industry-solutions/automotive-and-workshop-industry/</guid><description>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Page ID&lt;/strong>: 3153985855
&lt;strong>Last Updated&lt;/strong>: 2024-11-15T01:57:55.733Z&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>Success Story 3 : Automotive and Workshop Industry﻿&lt;span class="hx:absolute hx:-mt-20" id="success-story-3--automotive-and-workshop-industry">&lt;/span>
&lt;a href="#success-story-3--automotive-and-workshop-industry" class="subheading-anchor" aria-label="Permalink for this section">&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Wavelet is an entrusted solution provider to one of the most well-known European market players in the automotive industry (with currently served headquarters in Singapore and Malaysia). One of the key challenges faced by the client was the lack of customer engagement and personalized &amp;rsquo;touch&amp;rsquo; when executing their marketing activities. No software had been set in place to stay connected with customers and provide convenience for their financing needs.
The scope of the project has involved a CRM Application which consists of both Mobile Application and Admin Console. The Mobile application is running on Android and iOS which addresses the needs of multiple car brands. The Admin Console back-office system is a complete package that administers marketing events, promotions, member card privileges and custom messages. It also incorporates other versatile features such as invoice management, audit trail reports, target group management, updating of terms and conditions, and landing pages.
In addition to optimising the data exchange between the automotive business and end customers via an implemented CRM app, Wavelet has integrated the software to the current back-end ERP system for the automation of the financial module and invoice management. The system allows the car owner to pay their car loan directly via the app, with the data being pushed directly to the back-end system for further processing.
Furthermore, Wavelet serves several largest car servicing and workshop market players in Malaysia. One of the long-served clients is a renowned car servicing centre, established in the 1980s, with a wide network across the country. Servicing more than 15,000 vehicles monthly, the customer owns 20 branches in the Klang Valley and beyond.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3>The key challenges that the customer had faced with their previous system were:﻿&lt;span class="hx:absolute hx:-mt-20" id="the-key-challenges-that-the-customer-had-faced-with-their-previous-system-were">&lt;/span>
&lt;a href="#the-key-challenges-that-the-customer-had-faced-with-their-previous-system-were" class="subheading-anchor" aria-label="Permalink for this section">&lt;/a>&lt;/h3>&lt;p>Slow deployment for new outlets.
No support from the software vendor.
Manual data submission.
No standardization and duplication of item codes.
With the newly implemented systems, the management obtained increased capacity to control activities and have a comprehensive view of their business with instant access to critical data, anytime, anywhere while also gaining total control over multiple companies and branches in one single console. Additionally, the software has provided effective support to optimise cash flow and inventory, reduce handling costs and improve speed, eliminating duplicate data entries and minimising human error.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Food and Beverage (F&amp;B) Industry</title><link>https://www.bigledger.com/user-guide/industry-solutions/food-and-beverage-fb-industry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.bigledger.com/user-guide/industry-solutions/food-and-beverage-fb-industry/</guid><description>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Page ID&lt;/strong>: 3153854852
&lt;strong>Last Updated&lt;/strong>: 2024-11-15T01:58:35.705Z&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>Success Story 2 : Food and Beverage (F&amp;amp;B) Industry﻿&lt;span class="hx:absolute hx:-mt-20" id="success-story-2--food-and-beverage-fb-industry">&lt;/span>
&lt;a href="#success-story-2--food-and-beverage-fb-industry" class="subheading-anchor" aria-label="Permalink for this section">&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>&lt;p>With years of extensive experience in the Malaysia market, Wavelet team has been serving one of the largest Southeast Asia&amp;rsquo;s F&amp;amp;B brands with over hundred outlets across the country. With the strong ability to cater to the needs of multi-branch, multi-franchise businesses facing the high volume of daily transactions, Wavelet ERP system has been serving its growing business as a backend for the inventory and accounting data management of its direct branches and franchise businesses for many years.
The consolidated reporting from multiple separate entities is one of the key values provided by Wavelet, allowing the management to make informed business-wide strategic decisions with ease and convenience. The ERP has been integrated to the Point-of-Sale (POS) system for real-time data syncing between both software systems.
In addition, the Wavelet team has assisted to provide end-to-end consolidated solutions for the client&amp;rsquo;s bank reconciliation, allowing to automatically clear matching transactions and identify mismatches. The project implementation has covered more than just a simple automation of bank reconciliation activities, and has included the direct integration with one of the largest Malaysia banks. With the seamless integration across provided solutions, the entire process cycle has been automated, benefiting the client with the saved time and energy for the resource-consuming activities.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Industry Guide</title><link>https://www.bigledger.com/user-guide/industry-solutions/industry-guide/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://www.bigledger.com/user-guide/industry-solutions/industry-guide/</guid><description>
&lt;p>&lt;strong>Page ID&lt;/strong>: 3153822073
&lt;strong>Last Updated&lt;/strong>: 2024-11-15T01:56:59.787Z
The consequences of the COVID pandemic have had an unprecedented impact on the businesses worldwide. To survive and grow, businesses had to face the new reality of lockdowns and social distancing, and embrace online space as the only way to stay connected to their customers. With over 150 customers impacted by pandemic, Wavelet team has demonstrated its ability to guide and implement scalable cloud solutions at the fast pace - a &amp;ldquo;life savior&amp;rdquo; for businesses in the pandemic era.
Founded in 2003, Wavelet Solutions has been known as one of the most mature web-based ERP software providers in Malaysia, taking care of the consolidated accounting and inventory management for small and medium enterprises. However, the team has not stopped there. With the vision to become one of the major players in the market for cloud-native applications, the Akaun data lake platform was born. Based on multi-channel cloud-native architecture, with scalability, cross platform, mobile, and REST-API, it has aimed to reshape the future of businesses, giving an opportunity for significant competitive advantage over competitors.
Wavelet&amp;rsquo;s approach is different from other software providers. Driven by the vision of revolutionizing the way businesses would consume software services, the team is aimed to become an entrusted technology partner and consultant (rather than a vendor) to the local and overseas businesses. The digital transformation powered by their solutions takes into account business needs, workflow, future growth and goals, and most importantly - Who Your Business Vision is.
Serving customers of various sizes, including SMEs and large enterprises, from 20 different industries across 5 countries, Wavelet team provides much needed IT backbone and infrastructure to support their growing business.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>Operational Data Lake | At the Heart of the Business﻿&lt;span class="hx:absolute hx:-mt-20" id="operational-data-lake--at-the-heart-of-the-business">&lt;/span>
&lt;a href="#operational-data-lake--at-the-heart-of-the-business" class="subheading-anchor" aria-label="Permalink for this section">&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>&lt;p>In 2015, the team started to develop the next-generation app platform. Based on multi-channel cloud-native architecture, with scalability, cross platform, mobile, and REST-API, it has reshaped the future of a range of companies, by providing them with the unique cloud-native app solutions. The benefits of the operational Data Lake include, but are not limited to :&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>1. Integration Capabilities﻿&lt;span class="hx:absolute hx:-mt-20" id="1-integration-capabilities">&lt;/span>
&lt;a href="#1-integration-capabilities" class="subheading-anchor" aria-label="Permalink for this section">&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>&lt;p>With the advent of cloud, businesses are overwhelmed with choices of software applications in the market, aimed at automating their business processes, reaching out to their customers across multiple channels, and replacing their legacy applications with all new web applications. However, according to Gartner&amp;rsquo;s (2020), integration has become the single largest cost and challenge for the businesses to operate these disparate systems seamlessly. Typical system diagram before using Operational Data Lake:
System diagram after using Operational Data Lake:
The proposed Akaun Platform by Wavelet team has revolutionized the way businesses consume software services, providing them the much needed IT backbone at a fraction of the cost, with superior flexibility and scalability. The data lake - a single source of truth for your data - lies at the heart of the Wavelet applications, connecting multiple separate systems into one end-to-end seamlessly integrated solution.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>2. Diversity and Richness of Akaun Application Portfolio﻿&lt;span class="hx:absolute hx:-mt-20" id="2-diversity-and-richness-of-akaun-application-portfolio">&lt;/span>
&lt;a href="#2-diversity-and-richness-of-akaun-application-portfolio" class="subheading-anchor" aria-label="Permalink for this section">&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Wavelet handles the complexities of the ERP system, CRM, Point of Sales, Financial Accounting, Warehouse Management, Logistics and Delivery, Contact Centre, Digital Marketing, Inventory Management, Membership Program and various other business applications, and convert them into manageable applications (known as &amp;ldquo;applets&amp;rdquo;). Businesses are able to mix and match various applets tailored to their needs without purchasing a huge and complex system. Current Akaun portfolio covers a wide range of solutions, including :
ERP System
Financial Reporting Applets
Inventory Management Applets
Point-of -Sale (POS) Applets
Membership Program and Voucher Management
Delivery Management
Bank Reconciliation and Integration with Banks
Issue Tracker
B2B Module
E-Commerce
Integration with Online Marketplaces
Payment Gateway
Stock Take Module
Business Intelligence (BI)
Multi-Level Marketing
Tracking and Logistics
All applications are connected to the Data Lake serving as one single source of truth for your business, eliminating the hassle of double-entry and duplicated data. The Data Lake serverless database allows massive data to be stored and processed centrally, functioning as the data exchange across multiple systems.&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>3. Platform for Developer Community :﻿&lt;span class="hx:absolute hx:-mt-20" id="3-platform-for-developer-community-">&lt;/span>
&lt;a href="#3-platform-for-developer-community-" class="subheading-anchor" aria-label="Permalink for this section">&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>&lt;p>The platform allows any developer to embark on Akaun to utilise data lake infrastructure for the development of their applications for the various business use. With the comprehensive Akaun API, businesses can choose to consume the Operational Data Lake services within their existing legacy applications or they can develop a brand new web, mobile or desktop application without any server-based backend.
To explore more about Wavelet EMP solutions, Bigledger applications and integration options, you may visit &lt;a href="https://wavelet.net/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://wavelet.net/&lt;/a> and &lt;a href="https://bigledger.com/" target="_blank" rel="noopener">https://bigledger.com/&lt;/a>&lt;/p>
&lt;h2>AWS Partnership | The Power of AWS in the Heart of Solutions﻿&lt;span class="hx:absolute hx:-mt-20" id="aws-partnership--the-power-of-aws-in-the-heart-of-solutions">&lt;/span>
&lt;a href="#aws-partnership--the-power-of-aws-in-the-heart-of-solutions" class="subheading-anchor" aria-label="Permalink for this section">&lt;/a>&lt;/h2>&lt;p>Amazon Web Services (AWS) is the world&amp;rsquo;s most comprehensive and broadly adopted cloud platform, offering over 200 fully featured services from data centers globally. In addition, AWS is architected to be the one of the most flexible and secure cloud computing environments available today : known as the most secure software infrastructure in the modern market.
Leveraging on AWS solutions and being on the way to become the first ISV Accelerate Partner in Malaysia, Wavelet is able to provide the best value to the fastest-growing startups, medium and large enterprises in Malaysia and beyond—to lower costs, achieve agility, and innovate faster.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>